woke up from another one of psyches midnight fright displays shadow in the hallway
chanting through the haze coffee on the altar static on the screen
Crits in the walls, a velvet rope at midnight And a voice that softly calls, nobody's exactly normal
That's our favorite thing, we laugh like saints with eyeliner and a phone that never-
cards of breakfast like disaster is a farm someone hit the relics in the laundry by the
stairs someone's acting casual well conducting psychic prayers and somewhat in the candle
smoke behind the secret door a hidden hide priestess knows a little something more she
never makes an entrance she just suddenly appears fixes every
The cold's going underground again
Underground, underground, keep it cozy, keep it strange
Every haunted little heart in here is overdue for change
If the world gets loud above us, let it spin
And make the fuss, we've got one secret high priestess
And she's probably judging us
Show me that smile again
like eDreams
I guess I am boycotted. It's okay.
More like the trash to get stuff out and I know beat is on right now, but yeah, I mean you can go
there here talk about me you can actually watch me. I mean, I mean, wow. Boycotted, by the way,
with 80 people in the chat last night, you know, I don't get it. But yeah, I don't know.
Whatever she turn I look like I'm 70 years old by the way. I mean really oh
My gosh, well, this is Lenore
Nor are you look you're backwards and there's backwards right now. Oh my gosh. She's a massage in me
This is just her
You're oh you're just massaging my back. He's my little personal count masseuse
So anyway
Yeah, I guess it it mean it is I guess, uh, you know
Maybe I was just the only person on last night. I don't care if I have one person in the chat
I don't care if I'm one person in the chat not chatting. I don't care. I
Do this for the Lowell's the Lowell's whatever
Wow, and she's gonna she would be I would you know, I would just be streamer because she's it mean it is like
I am the content. Yeah, basically, but anyway
I guess Q, I guess, organized the boycott of my show and so, you know, stay away everybody,
you know, Q will get mad at you while Q beat you up.
Q is a little bitch, you know, I'll just say that, you know, he's not, oh my gosh, he can't
fight, I mean, it's like, all you can do is mace people, you're a little bitch Q, you
mace the fucking homeless guy, because you left your fucking clothes with him, what a
bitch you are, sad bitch.
Yeah, and your boycott is not going very well, you know, hey, what's up easy? Are you are you gonna stream easy?
I was gonna I was gonna go over there. Yeah, what's up, dude?
I know apparently like, you know Arthur was like, oh, I'm so happy
You know psychies everyone's boycott and thank oh shout out to Q and then Arthur
Yeah, well Arthur's just a little salty because I kicked him off the panel because
I don't even remember why. I had to kick out Q, I had to kick out RG, I had to kick out a few people, a clumsy being, I mean it's like, and then all of a sudden I had a great panel last night with Alexandra and Joni and Joe Shipley and it was a lot of fun, it was great.
You know great conversations, and I got kind of drunk right Arthur's big thing
He's Arthur is so fake. He's oh show. Oh my god. He's like, oh, there's a big like boycott against psyche now
You know shout out to Q. Wow Q's gonna Q. This is a person Q spits on spits on women
Mesa's homeless people
You know actually has gone violent IRL and it's like oh and he's like now. He's the moral authority, right this guy
It's other guy gamble already admitted to like
to lying about, you know, Zaya and stuff like that, trying to like, you know, make his like
predator hunter show or whatever he has, you know, like bring it some credibility, which he
it's like, now it's lost it, you know, basically Crystal Land, that's a great, I mean, great move
going to her show, right? But, you know, I know it will be, my gosh, this cat, look. Yeah, and then, oh,
Like, has no one seen Tom and Jerry?
I mean, does no one understand, like, you know,
cats are hunters.
They have, you know, they have a love of hunting
and they sometimes they catch mice.
Yeah, there's a big boy called on the channel.
I don't know, you know, Q, I guess,
has organized something or there's, you know,
so whatever, the link.
Okay, come on, here we go.
Yeah, so I guess the this channel. Wow, we had 80 people in the chat last night by the way boy caught it by the way
This is my backup channel and we had 80 people in the fucking in the fucking in the chat
Let's night, you know, it was it was great
That's an interesting
DX
GH CM and G her Z and GGR. What the hell hi Rudy? Oh my gosh, you know cats are gonna cat. Hi. Hi
Mr. Rudy. Hi, Rudy.
Yeah, my cats hate me by the way, the cat. Yeah, I know the cat the cat's absolutely can't stand me, right?
They're just like, you know, they're very very bad abused cats. Oh, is this Arthur?
Yeah, oh my god, Arthur's coming up. I
Can't believe Arthur's back
Arthur
Hello
You're muted, my friend.
I thought you were a boycotting Arthur.
Hello.
Friend of the show, Arthur, yeah.
Hey, brave little toaster.
Yeah, but I just want you guys to see
how unhappy the cats are.
You know, apparently they hate me, you know.
And, you know, oh, do I care?
Cult of Yarl, how about, I'll take one less person.
How about one less for me with you?
You can, you're gone from, you're gone from the chat.
How about that?
Oh, that was quick.
Is it a numbers game?
I just started, she's been on for a little bit, you know,
and, but whatever, it's like, you know,
I had 80 people last night, so I won last night.
Hey, thank you, I got a question, I got a question.
You wanna get to stay here?
Hey, Arthur, what's up?
There you are. Oh, good to see you. You look great. Oh, you look great. Oh, my gosh. Yep.
Well, we caught him. Yeah. Oh, thank you, Arthur. Oh, is it a sweep you there? Christine there?
I'm busy, thank you.
Are you gonna make a video of my face?
I am so sorry.
Arthur, your microphone.
Oh well, yeah, Arthur was a friend of the show,
but he's fired, by Arthur.
I mean, it's like, gosh, I mean,
it's like not a real friend of the show,
not too much of a friend of the show.
But, oh, okay, well.
I might have like several short episodes today. I had to I had to but we hey we got double digits in the chat
That was good. I'll be on tonight. I think I'm better at night, but hey charisma. How are you doing?
You know, I'm here with the I'm here, you know with these these these mistreated cats, you know
It's like a beat is like oh my god. He lets his cats
He lets his cats catch mice. I mean wow
And then apparently there's a boycott of the show that Q's organized Q the great moral authority of the of the panel verse
Let's all you know listen to Q and now what are people afraid of Q and Kate and
That'd be a cute couple Q not no pun intended Q and Kate wouldn't what an interesting couple that would make
You know talk about breaking the bed, but anyway
Yeah, I'm just gonna I just wanted to check in and let you guys know. Let's all like you know, we can all we can all go
Go lurk and beat us or whatever. I'm not allowed on the panel nor the chat. So, you know, apparently I'm like some kind of evil
Evil person in bad person. So but hey guys, yeah, they're absolutely delusional
And hey, we had a fun chat last night. We had over 80 people in the chat. We had a full panel
Well, you know, we had like
Full enough, you know, if four people that was good for me. So
I know some people are afraid, don't let these people scare you, okay?
Don't let these internet people scare you, you know?
To have whoever you want on your shows,
go to whoever's chat you want, be wherever you want.
They don't let people tell you what to do.
I mean, it's like, and as for the boycott, you know,
I'm, I'm, I'm absolutely fine.
It's been pretty, um, enjoying myself.
And so I just want you guys to know I'm still here.
Hey, what's up?
I mean, it's like, and I love you and, uh, you know,
Oh last night by the way not one person out of those 80 people
I did not have like one person I had to ban
I mean it's like because everyone was just being cool and so it must I don't know what it was astrologically or yeah
It's not Christine's show. It's not it's not beta show. It's and you know what I'm glad like, you know
Rg and cute. I'm glad a lot of these people are gone, right? Really really I mean, it's like
Like like I said the trash can take itself out. It's like, you know, these are not people you want to yeah
I thank you. I was I was you subbed and not snubbed. Thank you brave little toaster
You are brave, you know, you say and you know what you are people. I
Just take courage to stand up to like some of these bullies and it's like
Don't let yourself, don't let yourself be bullied.
Yeah, and you can see exactly how fake Arthur is.
Oh, oh, Psyche's show is dead.
Yes, and Bita's like, well, I don't know
because she was here last night.
You know, and thank you for like spending
some of your birthday with me.
Yeah.
And yeah, and I do like that show that pack yourself up show.
I don't know who's behind that, that's a good show.
Hey guys, somebody did contact me.
I don't know if it was pack yourself up or something,
but somebody did contact me privately about tricks.
But then it's like, I looked and it was somebody
like in the panel verse, I don't know if they saw something
in Craigslist or something and sent me to it.
Can you guys, I dropped my phone the other day and broke it.
So can you contact me please if you can?
and contact me again if you're watching this about that
and tell me exactly what that was
because I'm a little confused about that
or I don't know if you were trolling
or something like that,
but it looks like he's,
I mean, he looked very happy, healthy.
There was a big bowl of food out for him
and I think no matter what,
I know he's being taken care of.
I just, I looked on Craigslist,
I couldn't find anything about it.
So contact me again about that please
Something I'm I'm really concerned about
So yeah, I got I got a new phone
It's my new phone. I finally in the 5g network. Here we go. Oh my gosh, Lenore
There we go. I got a new phone
and so
Also has three cameras. I'll have some data. So maybe today's a day to go to the pier
Hey, what time is it? It's 12 to do but okay, maybe I'll go I'll go to the pier this afternoon. Oh
So now you just got a text
So maybe they are watching okay
I see
Okay, well, I'm gonna check this out follow-up. Okay. Thank you guys. Hey, Jamie. How are you? Well? Yeah, I don't know
Maybe I'll stay on for a little bit
You know, I do like smaller at least smaller groups
Hanging out with and I don't feel like just watching watching beat is right now
It's like you know just hear a bitch about me and stuff and say oh my god. Yeah, thank you Jackson Galaxy Psycho
Awakens, okay
Like it was excellent. Let's see if trip because anything interesting. I did see like there might be some
something. I mean, I'm Rumble. Let me see. Let me see. I'm just going to check it out. Okay.
Trip kick. Oh, and I guys, a lot of people were like banned by like some rogue mod or
something like that. And so, oh yeah, Tommy James also bitching about me this morning.
Oh, he's terrible. Oh, yeah. I'm just terrible. I know. I know. Well, you know, if I'm so terrible,
These some of these people
fucking
Kicked live streamers try squatting in a streamer house part two. That's kind of interesting
Crystal Anne versus clumsy on psychies panel. Yeah, well, Crystal Anne came on my panel. I was very nice
I was banned from her show and her panel immediately
and so
Here well, this is this is my show this is kind of funny this was when I had a fight with Amanda
Amanda you out there
Here we go. What is this one?
Number one worst snacks for your waistline.
What a weird commercial. Weirdest commercials.
Weirdest commercials.
Amanda, limiting words though.
Amanda, you wanna hear limiting words?
Go listen to Be The Stream tonight, where she had a woman saying F-A-G-G-O-T and N-I-G-G-E-R
about a thousand times, laughing all the way through, with everybody on the panel laughing about it,
and also saying gay people should die.
Go listen to that Amanda and a good adventure come back in the back and I mean I thought I thought you and Amanda were like like
Amanda went to Christine's and I heard like Christine talking all this shit and Amanda was kind of like
It's like they not really you know and she would say later
She's like oh, I like psyche and you know, but I'm not expected to defend himself. She is my mod and stuff and
was
just to be kind of in the
Enemy territory just like kind of like almost egging her on a little bit
And so then she hit a bunch of people in my chat and then she said that she was going to find my information too
I pushed her over the edge
Did it come from her or did it come from her?
She said on money for 20s panel. Yes later in the day and she went on several panels complaining about me
I mean, I don't know anything about that.
I just figured that you and Amanda,
ever since I've known you, Amanda,
I've been working on your panel.
I like Amanda, but until I looked at my blocked list
and she had blocked a bunch of people
and then she said she was gonna find my information
and I also told her,
Christina is straight out doxing my family
and she's like, well.
She just didn't seem to care so just didn't seem to care that much
She did say I did say tell me anything that defended me in that six-hour stream and Amanda did say one sentence
I like psyche and
Yeah, I think he's lost soul or something like that, but et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
I mean, that's all.
Then it's like, then it's like, then she goes back into the hate and says, I sent him, what's
the poem about?
And then she says about Danny Stranger stuff.
And I lied about what Bita said, and I didn't know what Bita said.
Bita said, as far as I can recollect, maybe I got the words perfectly right.
Okay.
But let me just think.
Give me a second.
I mean, I'm not perfect or anything like that, but would you would you honestly agree that this has like changed you for the worst?
What has changed me the streaming?
Or right. No, I'm how it's how it's getting compared to what you were
I'm stronger. Hey, I'm okay. I have a couple songs to sing. I'm stronger than yesterday
Yeah, I want to put it on the record that you're absolutely by I have a clip on my community post
Now read it now anybody would like to go watch the short it's on my community
Play now, man.
I can't play it now.
I'm on my phone.
Man, play it.
I'm on my phone, dummy.
I can't play it.
No, no, no.
Don't call me a dummy on my show.
OK, second of all.
Go to my community post.
I will right now.
People like, why are you yelling at me, Amanda?
You know what?
I am tired of you lying on me.
All you want is content.
And I'm going to play it.
play it now I'm on my phone
play it play it
I'm on my phone dummy
don't call me a dummy on my show
okay second of all
go to my community post
I will right now be there
people like why are you yelling at me Amanda
you know what I'm tired of you lying on me
all you want is content
and I'm not gonna be your fucking content
I am advising you
how many hours
three hours
How many hours were you on?
Stop slandering my way.
I am giving you notice to stop slandering my name.
Lady, stop slandering my name.
Do you understand me?
You are absolutely lying.
No, no, no.
I never said I was getting your information. I never said I work for the government. You are delusional
You said you live on a military base
You need help
You need help. That is not what I said
What's your channel name?
What's your channel name so you can see my live
Hello
Hello, it's all my community posts
What's your channel name so I can go over to community posts
Come on, tell me
You don't know my channel? Um, I've been typing in your cat.
What is it, Amanda Erickson? Yeah, it's Amanda Erickson.
Clumsy, clumsy. I know you're his friend. I don't know if you can try to reason with him.
This has been a downward spiral for about a week.
I'm trying.
You're absolutely delusional and you're listening to people also clumsy
I never hit anyone Kate and RG and that whole group told him that I was hiding people
He never checked the chat. They had him take my wrench
Okay, I made that decision. They didn't have me do anything. Okay, man
I absolutely did because I have it clipped also. I made that decision. But who was hiding people then?
I have no idea. I didn't hide anybody if I hit someone I'd tell you I don't give a shit
There were as many people that are my friends that had no reason to be hidden
Do you know there are other people here who have a wrenches besides me?
I'm gonna discuss it with you and stuff and you could have come up after RG
But because RG and Kate told you you went with it because you're paranoid and delusional and you just believe anything people tell you
You're paranoid and delusional. That's why you're not wrenched, okay?
Don't care about your stupid wrench
Your your channel is not that important people have tried to help you and you shit on all of us
What
You have lots of me five times this week.
Kate, did you see her?
Did you see her, Kate?
You have lied here five times to me this week.
Kate, I trust Kate.
Listen, I trust Kate.
I trust Kate.
Of course you do.
You know why you trust her
and you know why they want you to do this?
It's for content.
You're their local.
That's gonna be true.
They're low. You're being a little cow lady. I'm actually not a low cow
Cow in the cow game, okay? No, they are thriving off of this
You know what? I find it very disgusting that you were calling Bronzeberg the inward over
Disgusting human being
so i'm putting it on the record it's on my short if anybody wants to go see and it proves
that psych is a liar okay let's find it right now i'm gonna go right now okay there is your
check sure you are you're too drunk and high ruthless bitch i'm not drunk and high at all lady
okay i'm gonna go i've been watching you've been drinking all night quit lying about the facts
one two ruta rangers okay you're on something because you can't even comprehend you're on
Gives birth with a crown on your page.
It's none of your business.
Why do I have to answer to you?
Because I'm asking you nicely.
Uh, because I want to.
Okay, no, you didn't.
Because I'm fucking...
Okay, first of all...
It's an interesting video.
It's not live.
You don't have an audio clip.
Go to my shorts.
You have a chat clip.
You don't have an audio clip.
Okay?
So you don't know what you're talking about.
You know what I mean?
Go to my shorts and play the video.
Okay, play the video.
Okay.
I don't see it.
Shorts.
Okay.
There's the video.
Psyche, stop lying.
Okay.
Oh, let's play with you.
Let's make a beat.
It's not about Danny Stranger.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to play it right now, Amanda.
Do you want to see if people say it or?
Oh yeah, I want to be here for it when you apologize.
OK, let's see.
And God, you have to wait backstage
because you're in trouble, Goddy.
I'll just I'll tell you that.
OK, but are you just OK?
You can come in a minute.
But OK, Amanda.
Let's go ahead and play it.
Let's play a clip.
Okay, let me get it up and I'm happy to play it and let's see what it here's a sweet beta
Good hearted beta said about my friend that literally thought about beta
This is about a cliff that you accused me of saying on monies. I have pulled the clip. Please stop deflecting and play it
Not dyslexic. I'm playing it right now. Okay. You keep mentioning other people that
Please stop talking over. Okay. This is your page, right? Correct. I guess so it's so small play the one on the left. Okay
He doesn't like us and because it's all in the south the fucking list. I got my name on there Sam and media Christine
Well, she got a couple of other people on there. Okay
I live at Little Rock Air Force Base. Okay, that's an
I just go ahead and get into the punch. Okay, I'm 50 years old. All right
I can talk about now 58.
Two ex-NASA engineers just created a portable AC that is making old expensive models obsolete.
Going so fast. Can I slow it down a little bit? It sounds like the chipmunks are singing a song.
Okay, I'll go down if you want to okay. It sounds too fast for me. Okay. I'll just play like it
It's because you're high and you can't you can't deal with it. You didn't be going slower. I don't know
I don't know. Let's all listen to it. Hey, Tom's if you're big enough boy to come on down here
You just let me know I'm saying what I'm saying is I'm gonna let this be known
I don't I'm gonna say this directly on the channel right now easy
It's funny how I try to have a conversation like conversation with you like a man
And then you ran over the psyches who started talking shit
She doesn't like us and because it's all in the South's fucking list. I got my name on there saying man.
Dita Christine. Um, well, she got exiled. That was the end of the clip. You're playing it again.
I live at little rock and roll space. Okay. Okay. That's the fucking ball. Okay.
Yeah. I just got my friend Danny on that clip. Are you playing the wrong clip or what?
Um, excuse me. That is my clip. I don't know what you're talking about. You're drunk and high.
he literally lied on me and said that i said i was going to get his information
and that i worked for the government i just provided a clip that is done on betas is that
money for 20s panel that is not what i said okay let's play it again no this is okay this is money
for 20s panel okay well i don't okay well what about the danie stranger club that's what i don't
Okay, you're out of here lady. You were accusing me of slaying by the Danny stranger clip on beta show not about money for 20 show
So you're out of here. Okay out
What is this shit what is this bullshit as I get a clip about Danny stranger and what beta said and now she's playing some clip
Or she's yelling about an Air Force base and stuff. I mean
Clumsy who's that picture of?
baby's mom who is that my baby mama okay that's your baby's mama i thought you
like big girls looks like that looks like some kind of
is that benny you know you can't you can't tell who that is
no i don't recognize that person probably because of t
who is that is that still marie yes oh shit clumsy stop it i got you i'll
switch
Let's see it, Crystal, look, I had your back.
Come to the back real quick.
I was a guy.
Amanda, I didn't ask you, okay, whatever you said about the Air Force base wrong, okay,
that's one thing.
I asked for, you said I was lying about Bita and my friend Danny Stranger, and I told you
several times, where's the clip of-
Beat it talking about Danny and then you have this other clip and stuff like that. Yes, Scottie
Yeah, yeah, what the fuck am I waiting for?
Okay, so
Get rid of her get rid of her get rid of her
She's not gonna stop
I'm gonna say this one time and I need to go I do have a life outside of YouTube
You told me to get a clip
Okay
Where'd I go? Hold on
Yeah, hi beat is wide badge. Hold on it. So charisma wants me to play this here
Here we go. I don't know where I am, but okay, here we go. Let's see
I'm not sure what's on this clip. I'm just gonna watch it here. Here we go. We watch it together
You told us that I'm not gonna fucking tell you the truth. We are the world
The only thing you guys saw
The only thing you guys saw was okay. Wow
Yeah, they doxed a dox, right?
I mean, it's like I what because I doxed and they I doxed the guy that is
harassing criminally harassing me that has doxed me. I mean fair is fair, right? But um,
You know, I told them to stop
I told him, and I just gave away one letter of his address
every time he came in here under an alt
and started, was actually putting my address in the chat.
And so he was doxing me literally while I was,
I was just fighting back.
I mean, I'm not allowed to fight back.
I don't know, you know, you can keep my mothers
and my brother's names out of his mouth, you know?
We noticed he's gone into crystal, and I don't have anything against you crystal, you know
Okay, I'm sorry for, I'm sorry for my, I'm sorry for, you know, whatever I called you. Okay, I'm sorry too. Okay, I didn't know, I didn't know, like, sometimes you'll put pictures like that and I didn't know and stuff like that.
But yeah, I did have your back, you know, and, you know, I hope we can get, thank you for being in the chat and stuff. And you're loud here, Crystal. And it's like, you know, I don't have anything against you really. Okay, I mean, it's like, I think that you said some kind of outrageous.
things about me um that were not true and kind of offensive and um but you know I don't know
uh I don't I don't know you know I'm willing to I'm willing to forgive and forget I really am okay so um
You know, Jamie's a good peacekeeper
Peacekeeper for you know, and it's like, you know, you I can't I don't tell Jamie, you know, it's like
Like or not like and it's like and so and
You know, so
So she's a good she can smooth things over sometimes so I wanted things I love about herself. Anyway, um,
I don't know I was
Oh, I don't know. Today, I'm having not a bad day, not a bad day, but I'm a little sleepy,
and you know, I'll be back on tonight, maybe this afternoon. Oh yeah, I might go get fish
tacos at the pier this afternoon. We can have a pier because I want to try out my new phone
Hmm, let's do it now. Let's just go now. Okay, let's do it on the stream
Now I'm hungry. I'm like, okay. I'll just go ahead. I don't know. I don't care if it's happy hour or not
Let's try this out. I want to try this new phone. So
You see, okay, so okay stream yard
We'll go see what's going on to the pier today
Okay cookies, okay, there we go
I wonder, hold on a second, I need to figure out
what more stream yard's on and what count it's on.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, stream yard.
One second, guys.
And we'll have some fun.
This will be interesting.
Okay, so let me just check out what count it's on real quick.
Count, okay, okay.
Bound it use another account
Okay
Hmm
Okay back figured it out, okay
Okay, it should be pretty it should be pretty good actually it should I think this is a I
Think this camera is gonna be a lot better. Let me skip skip skip. Okay. It's like yeah
Let's go for a little walkie and my cigar. Okay.
Oh my god, that's taking forever. I'm so sorry. Okay.
How's everyone doing out there? Hope you're good. Drink some copy copy. Okay.
Because I was like I might either gonna fall asleep or I'm gonna go do something productive might as well some content, right?
Okay
Okay, finally I'm in I mean, okay
It's your studio
Okay guys, I'll be right back turn up
Hello
Crack back
Sure, it's not p-bombing me, okay
While you're in the app
Though they're wrong. They're going today easy having a field trip. Okay. Here we go
Okay, there I am
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
easy. Oh, here you are. Okay, I got it.
Hi. What's up, dude? How are you? I can't hear you. I have to leave again. I don't know
what the hell happened. I came in perfect and there's like no volume. Well, I just switched.
I just switched. What is that? Oh, not for me. Okay. I just switched my camera. This
Oh shit. Here we go. We're gonna get what you're getting for what you're going for
Choco all shit say less we're going to appear or the pier and
Oh, I guess we lost him for a second people don't give me a second. I'm a second. It says the new phone or new something
Yeah, please like, you know, I think the last night there was 80 people in the chat. Like, I know I know I was
Over there. She was bitching about that. It was like 80 people in his chatting, you know, like we can't have that
Well, I guess they're gonna organize over there, you know, everyone's got everyone listen to you by the way Q
He makes a homeless guy. He you know in his tent
He fucking has spit on a spit on a woman
Which is the same guy that they've been giving you guys grief about like OD, you know grief about it like oh
It's like you got him up there. Oh
Yeah, mom he porn bombed RG has porn bombed me
Lemons, he's poor mommy
And even like, I mean, this, this gamble person even admitted like that he's, he lied about Zaya
and stuff. He said, well, I call people PDFs, but I mean, that's anybody,
anything to do with anybody under 18 is a PDF. And it's like, you know,
no matter how wrong or wrong or what it is, it's like...
I think that we should like be reserving these really, really harsh libelous terms for actual
like children and stuff like that and not like, you know, I don't know. It's just, it seems like
really crazy to me. We just like throwing names on people, jackets on people for the
reputation to get ruined.
Exactly. Exactly. And it's like, and it's, and it's sad that that's, I think that's like the oldest trick in the book, kind of like how effective that, that, that term is, but it's like really.
It's like it takes the power away from the word, which should be like a powerful word to be used against actual, you know
Yep, hey, what's up page pages in the chat page. We're going to the pier. It's a beautiful day and we don't know
Here we are beautiful day in the neighborhood a beautiful day in the neighborhood
Harbor
Um, you know Alexandra like well, unfortunately, well, unfortunately or unfortunately, I won't be going with Q. Hold on a second
Okay, but um, but I but she didn't get like all these details
She like did research and it's like she did pretty amazing job with that video and it's a beautiful day here to see everybody
I love this camera though, this camera is actually,
there's three cameras, three at three lenses on the phone.
It's a 5G phone.
Got it yesterday.
Hello, hey.
Yeah, I need another phone for my trip.
I'm working on that right now.
There's a phone for my data,
but I can wait for some pieces to come over
before I start my trip.
I got some data on my phone today.
Yeah, I need to get more data. I need to get more data from foolish patients. This one is trash. I can't put a butterfly
Monarch butterfly
See it. Oh, that's pretty cool. Yeah
Yeah, this is a beautiful city actually here we are down there's a hotel there's hotels
My dad used to take me down here.
There's a good restaurant called the Blue Water Grill.
And a bunch of little restaurants.
I think it should be a nice day at the pier, actually.
The bike path.
Look at that car.
It's looking nice and sunny.
Yeah, it's a beautiful day.
It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood,
a beautiful day in the neighborhood.
Which should be mine?
Which should be mine.
Well, it should be mine.
It's OK.
So here we go, I think the pier is down the missile way
See there's a regular truck on the Portofino
There's really there's something on the seaside lagoon where they take the beach water or they take the ocean water and they fit it
It's a little like kind of amusement park. I used to go there as a kid and stuff. There's all these boats. You see all the boats
Sailboats. Yeah, so boats my own friend of mine is worth them. He used to shrink like do the shrink wrapping on them
Hi, how are you good? You're a psyche a friend of mine used to work over over in the Bronx where the boats be at and he used to do the shrink wrapping
Wow
Yeah, the shrink wrapping yeah on the boats
Yeah, this is well, but when it gets bad weather, they're not gonna use it for a while and they know it those shrink wrapping to keep it nice and good
And so here's the seaside lagoon
Beautiful redondo beach
This is like right
Don't know beach. This is where we have people stay tuned in so I keep my neighborhood
Yeah, here we go. I used to go. I think I might smack the first person that looked like you
Yeah, I
Don't maybe I'll maybe I'll find a boyfriend today or something like that. I don't know
It's like, um, I think you know, you know, you gonna be his boyfriend. So you got a little jealous at you
Yeah, I probably, I mean, but on Crystal Anne's show, she was like, here, do you want to go do the bumper cars and do basketball at the, at the, at the, what's that Russia?
I don't know this game, amusement park place, I forgot what it's called.
But she's like, and then he's like, he's like, if I turn down psyche, what chance do you think you have?
And so, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, you would rather.
You'd rather, I guess, date me.
You'd rather be with a guy that be with her.
A chick, chick, would've, would've put me.
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
So here we go, yeah.
That's a trend.
Let's go with psyche, let's go with psyche.
Let's go with psyche.
Like you should just now just fuck me up.
So here we are, here we're going to the marina.
Just Captain Kids with a big seagull, big seagull right there.
Okay, here we go, heading towards the pier.
There's a restaurant called Captain Kids.
Um
Okay, so how are we doing guys good to see everybody in the chat
How many people we got to build the psyche yeah, well, yeah 16 people which is like
$16,000 in the building shout out to the 16,000 in the building
Everybody know what time it is hit the like subscribe get on notification for your boys psyches. You heard $5 a read in the hollow
16k yeah
I just bought my cards today.
Maybe like sat at a table.
Nick has a good idea about that.
But here's like a door we have.
Here we have the Little Mysterious,
California Surf Club.
I think it's like a little secret society right there.
Okay.
Hello.
I don't know.
I'm thinking about getting me a lasagna.
A lasagna sounds.
I need a nice meal right now.
Oh no.
Pretty little maggot.
Oh, that looks cool.
I want to go to there that on torrents. I was born there right there. There's a raccoon on it
You gotta go to Persia. You gotta go visit Persia
Yeah
Cool stuff. Okay, so there's captain kids
Okay, this is exciting
Do I have full I have full 90% battery? So we're all good
Uh 90% people. He's a okay Gucci
So let's let's talk to the ocean right here
Um, this is beautiful. You can see this is all that see where it's all white. That is all like poop on those rocks
But uh psyche how about you got a fishing rod psyche? I
Know they are
You got a fishing rod psyche all you need to do is buy some taco bread and then we go fishing. I got you
Okay, okay, like I'll get a fish pull. I'll get a fish pull. Yeah
Yeah, get your own or make your own own fish tacos for one day
So there we go, look at this guy.
Then my psychiatrist, oh my God,
he got radiation from eating that fish.
You gotta watch it, people.
They're gonna say something crazy.
Yeah, that's pretty funny, like I was,
I, you know, Bita was saying, oh my God,
it's like, let's just cats go outside and catch mice.
Like, okay, yeah, and?
And so I like did like a little AI of like, you know,
as a black cat with a mouse in his mouth
and it made like a mouse fish.
It's like, if you look at it, it's like half a mouse.
That was the main purpose of,
domesticating cats is to get rid of the mice.
Right, and actually the plague spread because I guess the Catholic Church at some point
was killing all the cats, and then the rats, we get these fleas on them, and the fleas
were carried to the bubonic plague.
And so actually the plague is because they were killing cats.
You know, so don't fucking kill the cats, right?
But there, look at that.
This gorgeous guys
They hate right now, you know why they hate it because you could go IRL and they can't
Right, and it's like I'm gonna have a great time like I like here
They will never go IRL they tie the shoulder face. They hide behind cameras. They talk shit about panels all day
They ain't scared to show their face and go IRL
Right. Oh, it smells so good. It smells like seafood right here.
Imagine being a cake stand, you can't go IRL in your own building.
Right. I mean, it's like, they can't even, yeah. I mean, it's like, this is like part of the plumb.
That's how real people is. They can't even go, people that took shit online or they can't even go IRL in their hood.
online right now they said I mean they said we had an avatar and with nobody
basically on camera and you know I show everything and so you know so they're
good the bad the ugly sometimes you know but I'm always yeah is this amazing
though this is like a beautiful beautiful day I'm trying to make it full
No, hi Christine. How are you? She's not beat is so she's not the animal. So I know she's over here recording
Beautiful bird you see that one. Okay, we're almost at the pier
What you know about birdwatch and talking about beautiful birds?
Well, that's a seagull, I guess. Um, I don't know am I trapped in my trap behind here. I don't know if I can
There's the pier right there. Okay, so I missed the entrance. Okay, so here's the pier
You never get lost in your own neighborhood. I know it's it's terrible
Or I think I'm yeah, I have to go back a little here. It's right over here. Okay, not lost. I'm not lost
Okay
Like it's like you need a one of those on
The new the new
Freakin stand I forgot what it's called, but it keeps it more steady like all you gotta do is keep on there
And no matter how you move it'll be more steady
Yeah, I need I need the little selfie stick. I this is a new phone. And so I don't not even a selfie sticks. I forgot what it's called
Maybe it's a time for a drink yet, maybe there's some really cool bars with like live music
homemade
Is it 12 o'clock? Is it lunchtime?
Well, look at it. Yeah, it is it is one in the afternoon. Here we go. So here we are
It is what it is time to eat. Okay, look at this place has
Skateboards and you can buy paddleboard skateboards look can you trips sunglasses, okay?
There's actually a little spy store around here, too. I'll see the spy store where you can buy spots
spy equipment, okay, here's the boats
Hey fucking nice shit
Under the boardwalk, okay, I was a cute guy. Okay, let me see if I can
Change the layout we see
Layout here that better here
So where's the spy store the spy store I don't wonder if it's open. Yeah, there to see it the spy base GPS it is open
Look at this place
You can go and
That's the James Bond in there. It has all kinds of cool equipment. You wouldn't be it last time. I remember I remember you I remember when you went
Yeah
There's a Lucy Foss. There's
Find some if you got some high-tech gear that could scan the item before like you buy it and like you well
That's where they selling that for right now
Yeah, okay, like you buy cheap
I forgot what caught people do that like resellers. There you go. Uh-huh. Look at this place. Oh my gosh
Interesting looking people. Okay, a lot of people bring their dates here all over the
So if you want to go get a margarito something whatever you said you was gonna do I think you should because um, you know what I'm gonna
Yeah, they do they charge a lot for fuck what time is it you're a grown man. They're a grown man want to be or whatever
a little whatever
Then that's on you
Yeah, bro
There we go. Here we go. Here we go for stucco's
This talk look at the big there's a huge line out. So this is the oldest
Fish market in California. It is the oldest one. It's like I think it's from the 50s or 60s
It's called quality seafood. I can show you some of the live lobsters and stuff. Look at this stuff
Pretty amazing
Put your finger in there
Okay, so the males are going to be larger females are slightly small get lost the taco psyche crab tacos. Oh my god
There's live lobsters in here
You can see this amazing seafood you lost a hundred and nineteen dollars for that platter right there
We're getting three pounds of crab. Why did you bully?
Okay, so here we are
You can see this is packed. Um
Okay
They actually they love when I film here. Here we go
Hey, oh
I miss happy hour. Well, it's not even it would be Friday anyways. There's no happy hour. Okay. Anyway, Friday's come on
Might lose out on
Okay
Pretty fresh
I
Can fish tacos
Yeah, oh, yeah, or how much is it?
Okay, five dollars Friday. Oh perfect. Yeah
Yeah
That's it
That sounds like a great deal right there. Yeah, okay
You know how much they are on top of a big dating. No, actually
Okay, sorry about that
Then we'll go to skate park we can look at the skate park, too
Yeah, you went there last time too. Remember you I'll tell you oh extra time to ride here quick
Thank you
Yeah, thank you. Okay
Okay, we're gonna walk to the skate park with people skating around but yeah, it's a beautiful day a beautiful day here. Oh
And I do like to be friendly with most pretty good around here. There's the tourists
Okay, so
They're buying like little
Stuff at least nice little tables around here. I'll you know one of these tables
Um, how's everyone doing guys and you can see the large murals
New video exposes
Oh, yeah, I did I did see that. Um, yeah, exactly
Go check out
You know like Alexander reported yesterday. Oh my god. There's a guy with that to show she reported yesterday that um, you know
He did admit to lying and so
Yeah, look at this my god, this guy is hot
Sike
I do need to and like there's nobody at the skate park nobody's skating right now
But you can come here and skate all your heart's desire
For the skate park here. Okay, some cart wheels, you know, put the phone on behind your t-shirt that day
Whatever t-shirt you wear put the phone do some cart wheels spin have fun on the water dive in come out talk to the
Yeah, okay. Let me just sit here and smoke my cigar a little bit right now
I just um, I just I just came back from the gym the little workout
What took like four laps of swimming and they went in the steam room
Hmm, how's that? It's a great. There's a guy right
There's a guy on YouTube and you're like he's a black guy. I think he's in New York
It's pretty funny, but he goes in the steam room and it's like underwear and stuff and he films it
And then and then people figure out that he's I mean some people don't know that like my balls are hanging out
I don't know kind of fun. I'll go with my towel on. I'll go with how you supposed to go with a towel and a rag
Yeah
But yeah, then he then he starts working out in the steam room and it's like wow, I mean that's pretty crazy. Okay, so I'm gonna walk
So this is a nice little day at the pier, you know
It's kind of packed a little bit
Well, it's not too packed right now, but it looks like you know still early in the day
It's like what in the afternoon?
So let me see who's hi everybody in the chat. How's
Nobody's in the back, you know, I guess there's them
But um, let's have a look
Okay, but yeah
Okay, yeah
Because I can't like necessarily keep my eye on the chat right now. So just keep your eye
Thank you
Okay, I'm gonna put up my cigar
Okay
So my kick is that Brandon Q 92 that's him
Well, I mean that's an interesting to the other queue
Q45 they are different cues. Okay, okay, but okay, here we go
Yeah, my car. Okay, here we go. Okay. I mean, so I don't want to burn myself. Okay. There we go. Okay
Okay, here we go
See
Okay
You're freezing you're freezing try to move a little bit over somewhere
That's why I pick up the food. It's like it is inside and so yeah, it's a little it's a little bit freezing in there, but
Okay
I'm gonna pick up my food. So you oh you watch watch the very career. I'm gonna pick up the food
I'm looking at the chair right now. I know this man modern it is good. Take care of it for me
I'm just looking at the chair. I'll drop the link though
Hi for John
Okay, ready yet
It was a fish taco
Okay, so I'm ready out there
Yeah, well, we're still waiting I it is a yes
No, why you don't get why you don't never got you never got lobster tacos. How much is the lobster tacos?
Lobster tacos. I don't know let me see look look at the
There's a $150 platter right there one and a half pounds of shell on shrimp
half of a pound of lobster, half of a lobster,
a pound of snow crab, eight sides of the garlic bread.
There's a $190 lobster clam bake.
Yeah.
Can I get a snow crab taco?
Ooh, that sound good, snow crab taco.
Oh my God.
Good looking, looking at all the food.
Jesus, I'm a fat ass. I would have been my go-to lobster taco or snow crab taco. Oh my god
Man listen, I'm a fat ass like you think man
God darn it. You don't lost him
I'm over here
Holding it down now for psyche everybody give him a few
Picking up his orders. You're gonna jump back in. I'm like walking back. You know, that's the pattern
Yeah, every time he had to sit a fish taco spot. We always lose them
So just hanging it you already know he got against fish taco once a month at least once a month
Me too. Me too. I'm gonna twist it, but I would have went but I would have got the crab legs
Toss that in a taco. No shot. Let's go. Just pull the meat out for me boy. We'll do what you do
Take all that got in there put it in the put it in the taco. Let's go. Oh
My god
So they boycotting your boy. They they say boy cause I say they be um
I said shun like the Amish you gonna shun me
You're gonna shun me out the community. Don't let him up. He's a bad guy. Oh no. Oh, no
So little everybody doesn't drink it right now
There we go. There you go days back days back with his long hair. He don't care
Hi here
Thank you. Thank you. Can you but can you imagine me without long hair? Can you imagine me bald?
No, but you probably look good
Yeah, how long is your hair is pretty long, huh? I've seen I've seen pictures my hair was pretty long
Okay, okay
Rub it off the stone. Okay, so it feels awkward
Been a long time without it
Well, let me get sorry guys for like a little a little the glitch. I'm probably gonna glitch again when it
Get my
Everybody knows if they know you watch your video every time you go to fucking fish taco you break out every time so it's like
Sorry
anybody else welcome to join me and bring new conversation and you know we
want to know how your day was and whatever the case might be um how you
feel about boycotting um how you feel about this and that whatever the case
might bring bring it up to conversation
oh my queen's here now
Yeah, well, I mean like because of that we're all picking on ghosts and stuff like that
I think that he hasn't been back that night you in the show
Yeah
Did you do where you're there? Do you remember that night with the ghosts and stuff like that and then Alex started calling out PDF and stuff Alex McQueen and
Alex were crazy on her because Alex don't like that shit when it kind of kids one thing I respect Alex
He goes off on anybody they got involved
But it wasn't a kid but easy it wasn't a kid
It was this 20 year old woman and then he
Okay, yeah
Well, he was talking to this grace woman who sounded like she has the mental capacity of a six-year-old.
She was crying and stuff like that. He has no problem talking to her and stuff.
I mean, it's like, jeez, I was like, I don't know, double standards.
But, um, yeah, he hasn't been back since then, so.
Right now, a lot of people don't understand Alex more than hate him. At first, everybody hated me,
me, but now understand him a little bit more.
Well, I'm trying to say is that that was not fair what they needed to go.
Um, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Nobody confronted him yet. Only only only me because I got the balls to confront him and nobody confronted him yet
Well, why is why is she loud on panels? I'm that's what I'm on an understanding
Like it's like, you know, you know, you know how panels get how like there's some drunk idiots
They know somebody's gonna get a huh, right?
They hoping and praying somebody get a get a huh for people to have something to talk about and then shame you for
Getting on her getting on exactly. Yeah, exactly. Now. We're on the same page. Yeah
Exactly and a psyche psyche is complex. She's like a catfish. Yeah, it is complex
It is it's not like just like so so cut and dry. I mean this one is 20 years old
Okay, first of all, and so they're letting her on the panel. Did you let Alex in? Did you let Alex in? You said Alex was here
No, no, it was they called that's when they call for somebody named Alex that ordered something
It was not I wonder why it's taking so long. It is taking a long time, but you know, it's worth it
Let's see
There is somebody in the back. I see three people
Okay, well, that's I think it's one of mine. What I mean. Oh, probably one. Yeah, what I mean is mean
But it was my house
Actually, it's kind of cool. I have my camera on at home so I can like look at my alarm. Oh, it's pretty awful
Bustles with rice
Oh
Some people's good to take pictures
Now look out for them on the choice
Take all the pictures you can
Psyche I'm gonna
Check out a receipt, but I have no idea what my number is. Okay
You have to drop your number in the back chat one of these days and I'll call you off of text-free and then I'll teach you how to
The noble wine the noble wine
Second you're glitching
We are on Glitch Central right now.
If you're there, stick to it.
Yo, don't, yo, for those who are watching right now,
can hear me speak and watch it, Psyche Glitch.
Don't this feel like an old school DVD?
Don't you feel like you were in the early 2000s
talking about, yo, clean to this, clean to this?
Yeah. Yeah. Wow.
Oh, it's okay. I'll let's walk around.
Yo, that's all it reminds me of right now.
I'll show you the dollar, yo.
Oh, they got an arcade? Oh, we lit.
We lit. Check. You gotta pass by at night time
and check if the arcade's open at a certain time.
But time opens.
I think it closed down.
But actually, I've seen all the...
I used to have rides and stuff. I used to go for my birthday.
And I used to get, like, a $20 roll of quarters on my birthday.
And go and play arcade games.
That was fun. I mean, it's like, I don't know.
I guess they don't have...
Old-fashioned arcades anymore, but look at the ice cream not probably really good ice cream authentic Mexican seafood
The boss chef
Let's see if anyone's skating yet
No, the skate park
No more glitch
That's one guy skating somebody clean the DVD that's what happens like you think the DVD
There we go
Right now. Okay. You can see the boats. Okay. There you go.
Imagine you find a skateboard, right? A random skateboard is in good condition. Will you take it there, right?
Um, sure. I mean, it's like there's a little there's a place you can buy skateboards around here too. I said
Yeah, it's like a big what if what if what if psyche that's what I like to say. Oh shit bear barrels at seas
You can ramp one of these boats the whale watching there's a whale watching boat. That's a glass bottom. Oh, yeah
No, that's why I call Barry or I see cuz once they motherfuckers jumping and they hit that front of that boat
You're gonna be Barry motherfuckers
Yeah, look at this place. Okay. So here we go. Hey, but look at me. Look at me. I got it with, um, um,
We had to go diving to see sharks
Helikens up here
There's like yeah, when I was on the trip I went diving I saw sharks
Such sharks. Oh my god. I've been to Hawaii and you could go snorkeling
I swear to God that I caught a little bit of it, but I
Fucked up on the camera. I was so excited. I didn't get to record it
And that's the guy that had a good go pro. I never received a video, but I tried
You know, yeah, good go pros. Yeah, if you can, you know, I even cash happy money for you
No, don't worry about it. Just send me an email give my email. He never reached out. I'm like fuckery. Oh, look at that. Look at that
Callicans
Was swimming with the sharks it was friendly friendly than the people online kidding me there's a
We're watching cruises. That's crazy, right? Yo, how sharks was more friendly than the people online psyche. I
Don't know. I don't know, you know, there's something there. Some sharks are very gentle, you know
But people are let's make this yeah, I got to touch them. I was touching them. No, I was I was I was curious
I had the snorkel gear on nigga. They dropped the cage. It was like
I felt like they put it to the point where we fight.
We was trapped in that motherfucker.
The water was just barely there.
It didn't come up and get the air.
And we go back down.
Oh my god, that sounds fun.
I've never been scuba diving.
But yeah, there's a guy on a show called Naked and Afraid.
And he's like a scuba instructor over here.
There's these new girls.
Sike, I filled up for that show.
I said video twice.
Were you naked in the video?
Yeah.
I
The fake bag and all I just like to ready send video the bloody feet motherfuckers. Let's go
Let me fun to watch though the audition tapes for that show, you know
Let me see. Okay. Well, we're gonna try again. Let's see if you're not gonna go all out them
If you're not gonna go out on a dish it for a show that you were to try all that
Yeah, you got it
You got it. You got it. You got it. Okay, so
Yeah, actually like that guy Tony has like a channel of me and he's like here's say he's bothering people at the pier
So I was a pretty drunk one day and I was calling out to people, but you know no one really cares
Oh shoo person, which you mean bothering
Bothering is being a nuisance. A nuisance is causing trouble. You're not causing trouble. You're being socially
Active right now, which means saying hi to everybody. How you doing? You want to say hi to live?
You're being socially happy, you know, say so for those who say that you're bugging
Out there throwing eggs and decking people for no reason
There's my taco
Let's go
Let's go. I look like a yummy. My mother fucking Tommy. You see it, huh?
Yo, does it got avocado does it got avocado?
It got no, it's got like a salsa. It's got a white sauce. I forgot to ask for a lemon
Spiky wait till you try wait till you try a real um
Mexican you could say let's let's say Mexican fish taco right from a real
Mexican with the Mexican green and red sauce and oh my god
I'm gonna throw some avocado on there, I'm telling you, you would have been like
Ayo, oh shit
what they said in the chat, finally somebody wrote in the chat, let's see what
Here we go she said
Oh my god
She give a little tip for that meal right now. That should look good. There you go a lot
I'm mother back out for like 10 minutes. Hey, all of my fish tacos. Oh
Yeah
Okay, I got a spot in Florida. Yeah, listen, I go for fish tacos too, so I
Making me do it. It is like it is like it is like a lot of fish on it, too
It is like a foodie. So you show me that food. I feel like I feel like pigs right now
I give my left nothing
Oh gosh
Well, that's that's how foodies really be feeling though, you know, like they're like, oh my gosh
Yo, you ever you ever saw I saw a real foodie on the training and how he was reacting
I'm like in the back of my mind. That's how I be thinking, but I don't be saying it
God damn this thing's out loud with it. That's so good. Oh my god. Oh
My god, well, look at this. I'll sit on the bench right here
It's like a beautiful day. It's just like it's like there's a beautiful breeze
Okay
Here we go
Look at the drip you saw the drip. Oh my god drip drip drip drip. What sauce they put on it
They put landmine with what's the flavor?
The bite
Yeah, very nice breeze awesome there beautiful they have a nice day. Yeah, oh here we go
Yeah, we got the ocean breeze is this a really beautiful day actually
Here we go up
There's a little park you cut through and then go to the liquor store
Already been there this morning. Did I go this morning? I did
But um, yeah, here we go
it'd be nice to live here like on these like these are great views but there's there's also imagine
imagine being so close to the ocean and be on the other side of it where it's like you know what
we psyche psyche say he's gonna rent me the next apartment next to him i was like that week i'm down
Have your neighbors and they're really nice
It's good that you know your neighbors, you know, I was listening to somebody's live the other day
I don't know what it was or where or even the short night. Uh, somebody don't even know their neighbors
It was like, I was like, oh shit. How you don't know your neighbors. I know all my neighbors
Well, they're nicer than the other people that live there
Couple of couple of them we almost for it like, you know, I don't give a fuck
Look at this nerd second. It's hangry
I got 12 families on one apartment one floor in one floor
There's like
That's 12 apartments on one floor
Okay, I mean you get another bite of this. Aye. Aye. Aye
As you should as you should maybe you should sit down and stop walking and just enjoy the air like they always say psyche
Oh touch grass and you're outside. You know Sam so I think you should sit down on the grass and eat your food
Well, there's grass up here
I'm going a little higher down like a little not like a oh, yeah, just a little like a little lunchbox for you
You know I'm saying
Lots of walking. I hate people that even even like I'll do walking in here, too
But that's if we're on a goal. It's more snack
Also down right here
Okay, oh
They got something by nose, okay, oh gosh, okay beautiful day
Yeah, really there's a beautiful breeze. It's like there you go
But it's like I won't be surprised. I would be surprised at a cat or a squirrel pull up and like you'll say give me get some of that
Yeah, well, let me see big grilled fish. Here we go
some more
What you do is like you set the phone down nice and comfortable behind the box or some shit
And then you sit on the side and then get your food
Thank you. I'll help you. I'll help you. You're just like I'm gonna I'm gonna help you be like Peter
I'm gonna help not if you don't want it. You don't gotta but I know how to do the um, the nano small one shit
I'm gonna teach you
The wine
No, no wine like no matter what happens. Nobody got to take it back
Yeah
Okay, but then after the show it goes to regular. So if you're not putting it
And if you don't put it private and be there's like a waste of time
So I'm like psyche keeps his videos to watch show him you like be this high to video
So that's a purpose of why she does it that way. So and I do the same so I have to learn it
And I figured it out. Well, all her videos go on to rumble and
So you can watch her whole shows on rumble and stuff and
See everything, but I don't know how rumble how you how you think how he does it without me with the poor moms
I'm about to start re-streaming everybody's live straight from rumble
Okay, I'm gonna
That sounds like a good plan
Everybody's alive. Hey, 28. I'm gonna review them as they live on rumble
Stay true to you guys on a rumble. I got like one video out there
Yeah, I got a rumble account. I think I'm psyche awakens learn rumble. I don't think oh, maybe I'm cool to psyche there
I don't know if I changed it, but here we are now
I'm gonna do lives on run over and get feedback about what they talk about the whole day
Okay, so here we are on a
Had a lot of somebody goes live if I support you I'll be like say if psyche you go here
So you're gonna be like, oh, you run rumble talking
I'll just give him my opinion psyche. You should have did this you should have did that
Okay, well, there's the yeah, there's my liquor store. Okay
Here we go. We got a liquor store. Yo, thank you. You ever try buzz balls. Yeah
Yeah, it's pretty good. It's pretty fucking good
I tried it the other day and like I googled a good recipe to drink it with and it was fucking awesome. I ain't no fucking lot
whoo
Yeah, I bet I've been drinking the beatboxes
No, look up. I psyche I started just drinking them straight look up a nice recipe
It's more in your flavor that you like and showed him like and showed him the beatbox and black
How can I make a good drink out of this since you mess with the AI is gonna is gonna show you something crazy
You gotta fucking be like, oh shit, that shit tastes great
Here we are it don't get you too drunk, right where you acting like a fool, but it gets you drunk to be right. Oh
Gosh, okay, here we go. I'm trying to say say yeah
I'm gonna I'm gonna try that I'm gonna I'm gonna maybe I'll see what they have something right here today
I'm making some caution. Yeah, make some concussions of drinks things gonna be like oh psyche's making three
Emotions now, but I can hear jokes now. So let me joke about it now before anybody else say they bite off my nuts
Okay, here we go
That's the dirty laundry. Take it dirty. Take it dirty as laundry over there. And they're gonna get stink-ass thongas. Oh, let me stop
Here is a store
Yo, this is so yo one of them say yo one of them say oh, I want to go get wax. You sure it wasn't a cobweb removal
Thank you, they say your fingernails always dirty which one of them you was being a poppin. Oh my god
There's this this uh, there's a restaurant here. Okay, let me stop easy
Okay, here we go
Oh, we're in the liquor store look for the fuzz bowls fuzzy fuzzy
There's a couple look
You drink my look you gonna be fucked. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Thank you. Thank you. Look for um, they got um
It's cut waters look for cut water
In a little can yeah
They got it. Okay. I don't know they have everything it looks like for look real good
Really look real take a second take a second scan through there check if they got cut water
Green chic
Just ask for a second. I think they might water I found it. Thank you. Don't fuck you up psyche
Trados pick your favorite flavor. I'm telling you try those for me tonight. I even give you five dollars to buy more
Right now Bob off by one extra one for five hours. I'm gonna send it to you right now. Okay. Okay?
I'll grab one more
My tie sounds good
That's three. Okay. Can I get and can I get two um two cigars and then can I get um two backs?
Thank you
Okay, guys here. We are thank you easy
By three of them
Hey guys, yep and perfect, okay
Go you there. I think they just know
Thank you so much. I got it. Yeah, I'm telling you to drink that song. It's like that's that's on me right now
We'll give you one extra me. Oh, yeah
Yo, I swear tonight you gonna be like easy. I'm I think I'm not drinking those no more
Thank you so much
Yo, be ready tonight. It's gonna be a lit night. Yo, I swear to God everybody
There we go. I mean, I'm gonna start drinking now when I get home
Yo watch
When they first came out I
Was it I was on a trip and now and I was I was I was going to start so I wanted to drink and my modellos was out
So I grabbed three of those of the Long Island flavor three to four of those or six they sell them out of four in a case
So I grabbed four by the next you know, I woke up on a beach, but naked on on the beach
And I see my clothes behind me like I was wild and I don't remember nothing. I don't remember nothing
Yeah, it says they're they're 12.5 alcohol. So these should
When they first came out there was just a little bit stronger
Wow
They're still good. They're still good. Let me tell you that
We go
No, the first time I ever woke up like that. I was like, yo, I never did a blackout like a fucking movie scene
I never did that shit
Wow, here we go. Okay guys we're almost home. It's just a little
They used to be this great
Don't get addicted to them psyche. There's so many flavors. There's gonna be something you might like or something
You don't like but yo, drink it all get it over with I got a I got a my tie at Margarita and
I'm gonna what other I think a Long Island iced tea. So all the long eyes tease on me
The long hours tease on me when you drink that one. They'd be like, this is on easy. Shout out to you
Okay, for sure. That's my favorite drink. That's my favorite liquor. I
Don't care how nobody
It tastes good. I love it. I love that thing. That that flavor is just just amazing to me like everything else
You know, but
I don't know. I just hit the ooo button on me. I
Don't like like vodka flavor. I just I like, you know sweet drinks like, uh, you know
I like I don't like I don't like the flavor of alcohol like it makes with game rum this that is a mixture
Yeah, it's a ready. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, they got it's got everything it's throw everything
Say like that shit. Just ooh
Always never fail
Never and when I was young
I said I should drink a lot of gallons of those and that's that was my go-to
Why you like this? Well, you don't get expensive shit. I don't get the good shot. This is what I like
Trouble that shit. Yeah, she's good. Yeah
Yeah, what you love get what you love here we go. So I'm just one walk away from my place. I'm walking pretty fast
Okay, got my taco
Oh look it's a squirrel. Oh, it's the squirrel YouTube YouTube audience 2.0. It was chillin with psyche
He's gonna make a video of you know, he's gonna make a video
I don't think the chat is really really quiet for 30 people in the chat and no one said anything
We got 30,000 people up in here
Yeah, I guess so, but I think they're all being very quiet. I just don't know
I mean, it's like I eventually will read it. I mean, I don't know. Maybe it's broke
Once I see the ones I click on it and I start you know reviewing this shit. Yeah
It's like I'm the most watched boycotted show in the world. You know, it's like
You and me both psyche come on they try to get me out the system too
It's okay. They're dying they dying psyche when I say that they dying they dying
Well last night the chat was on fire. I had Alexandra up. I had my friend Joni up and I had um and Joe and
and
With the chat, I was I was I was to I was to I was tuned in to about yeah
Toon thing to that kept on jumping around because it was a lot
It was a lot of other things going down the man other panels I watch and especially the a1
It was a lot of it lives going on. So I was just jumping around
But really it's like this is the most watched boycottage show and there were for boycottage the show and having 80 people
Like that was the most people I've ever had on this channel because this is my backup channel, right?
I used to have a hundred about a hundred psyche, but that's cuz they
You know what? I'll do it again. I promise I will I'll have I'll get a hundred people here tonight
We'll see I actually I do have some people that can I put my
Put my link on reddit and stuff and then a lot of people will come
Uh, it's like, I think their name is dumb, but I don't know since it's a fallout
I had a ball with beta with clumsy with
Be my case if I be my case. Oh lord, I'm going back on the streets like no tomorrow. They're gonna be like easy though. Stop going live. Nope
Okay, I'm almost home. I'm like easy taking all the screen time all the screen time. Okay, if I'm okay
I'm gonna stay on live showing something go in place. Thank you
Thank you. We're almost back
There's a there's you can see there's a there's a there's a power plant, you know, they they film Britney Spears crazy
crazy
Just they film that right there
Um, I don't know that song. I don't know that song. What's wrong with that one? Crazy. I just can't speak. I'm so excited
I'm in too deep. Oh crazy and it feels all right. Is that no hold on that back to your boys or is that bringing spirit?
No, you drive me crazy
Okay
I was a two-part fifty set all of games to you want to be a jazz motherfucking shit
Remember the life I lived completely different from yours like it's like
No, no, I like I listen to I listen to two bucks later in life, but my best friend in high school was like this like
Well, yeah, yeah, you're technically older than me. So, um, yeah, you probably like
Later, here we go. I'm growing up and you listening Britney Spears and shit
Oh, well, I mean Britney Spears. I mean that was like that was like when I was in high school. She came out with um, with the
um, what's what's the first song
God, let's see baby, baby, baby one more time or something like that, or
I know I don't have to listen to
This is still out there, but if I know
Okay, well, I'm home. I'm home. Oh
I'm hosting for 420, but I've been on you ever since so like fuck that shit. I'll be right back. It's easy
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna hold you down. That's right. Do your reconnection. You know that bullshit
Shout out to everybody that's still here. Shout out to the 30,000 people that's still here. You already know. Thank you for joining
Thank you for staying tuned. Yo psyche just bought the cut waters. This shit put me on my ass
Let's see what's gonna happen. It's like you ain't gonna be too young. This is gonna be my spaz out tonight
I hope you don't hope you hold it down. I need no plan. You know psyche hold it down like Nino Brown
Don't spaz out that shit go fuck you up that clean
Yo, thank you. If you drink all three of them tonight, bro, let me tell you
I don't know what might happen to you, but I wish you the best of luck. I'm gonna tell you the same thing when you come back
Yo shit, what the fuck?
Damn, I should never told me to get that shit. He might spray or they might oh my god
Oh, thank you. Thank you. Don't do it
Don't do it. How much was it? It was a kind of cheap psyche. Let me know what to get back
I gotta ask the pricing on that because those shit is good. Those shit is good. I can't even front
Oh, they're $4.00. $4.00 each
All right, there you go, there you go, $4.
Don't spaz out tonight, try your hardest
to enjoy the leaker and not spaz, please.
Wow, it's actually been, with 30 people in the chat,
it's been 20 minutes since anybody said anything.
Wow.
That is like the chat broken. I don't know
Wow, that's part of the best part of the of the box on boycotting, right?
Don't write
Your content is not worth watching since nobody's writing but just don't care fuck it just keep on doing what you do
You don't say it
Right, so don't fall for the gimmick don't fall for the gimmick. That's probably what they want
They probably writing each other in the background. Let me many of these people's in the background like oh
Don't write psyche. Oh, because if you go there, this that yeah, oh shit. Here we go. Here we go. Isn't the more I love those it's
Let me know if you need more if you need more, let me know you go go back to the store before it goes
Tiki rum my time. It's time to start guzzling. It's like one something over there
Okay, almost two o'clock two fourteen in the afternoon and so guys ready for uh
Ready to watch? Here we go. I'm gonna drink this one. Go with your favorite one. Go with your favorite flavor first and then go with Long Island and then go back to the least favorite.
Okay, and I guess I got a margarita. Which is the third one.
Oh yeah, that's how you drink them. Oh, they all look good though. I mean, a strawberry margarita is pretty good too. Okay, so let me see.
Strawberry margarita might be last. Okay, I'll drink that one last.
Or Mai Tai, Long Island, and then Strawberry. How fast do I drink it? Do I drink it in like once?
I think cuz I yeah, I drink I drink fast. So uh here. I'm gonna make us bigger. Oh, so my shit. So my shit
No, no, I just made it bigger. I just made it bigger. God. So your hand moved over. I'm like, who's here? Yeah
I got a little coffee left too. Okay. So there we go. Okay. I thought Alex your boys would be like psyche
No, don't pass out tonight my man
I'm gonna send you to go get more co-orders though easy. Go get naked without how you're gonna do
Yeah, but it's like I think people it is sad that people are afraid I think I think did I have a little modello before I don't know
I don't remember. I was blackout that day. I was just I think that was too much looking for me
Easy can I get five more dollars?
I just did that off the arm like
You don't got to do no favors for me. That was just by that like by the long bow actual one
Yeah, by the extra and then the crazy the actual one was long I last eat
Okay, we're gonna taste this one. This is the my tie Tiki run start off with my time. I got more Delo. So cheers
I strong oh
Sure, oh I can't see your face the cats in the way Lenore move when nor oh
I told you, I told you, you gotta be here tonight.
Gonna be at one hell of a night.
Oh my God.
It's like you're looking at me at the end of the night.
Watch, if you need one more,
I'm gonna send you to go get it.
I might wake up naked on the beach.
Okay, yeah.
At least I might wake me, yeah, I'm telling you,
that's the type of shit that I...
I drunk three long, four long islands.
When I woke up, I was like,
see the beer can behind me and one in my hand,
one behind me and my drawers and my shirt.
And my shorts is a little, like before that.
I'm like, what the fuck I did?
Like, like, like half, like a quarter of a mile down,
you see all the bubbles over there sleeping.
I'm like, oh, shit, what the fuck?
I woke up like, whoa, I never,
I'm never drinking that when I'll have somebody next to me.
Look at this cat. Look at this cat.
Like I'm not having somebody, somebody gotta hold me down. Hold me down because I know I'm out the spies out tonight. Watch this.
They're gonna be like, yo, E2, E2!
This is cat and sweetest.
Maybe that cat. It's like he said, ooh, that's strong. That's strong.
No, that's stronger than the voodoo. That's stronger than, um, did you ever have po loco?
Oh, I've had more local. Yeah, it's stronger than that. I think so. I mean, it's like I think I'm telling you that shit
Hey, right now. It's like you know, it's like if you take like two more things like the back with the next 10 minutes
You can play. All right
We need a chaser. Hey, look at Lenore. She's so
You're telling you site you take another zip like two more tips in like a like two minutes
You know in 10 minutes. You can play. Yeah, that's fine. That's good. Look up
Yep. Oh my gosh, isn't that pretty? Yeah
Like daddy, I know you about to start some shit up here. Go keep my love just late on. I'm not gonna be here
Why she look like the new miss cat I'll call the new miss she does she looks a little bit Egyptian
I like it. Yeah, there you go. Okay. Oh my god. There's
Yeah, just a good cat. Hey
Well today she was on my she goes on my shoulder like this, you know, you put on my shoulder
a little cry daddy like come on
Yeah, she doesn't want to love you. Why you move me?
There was a little cry right there
Favorite right here. Now she's gonna be a little angry watch you gonna be a little angry. Oh, let's get back to block the screen
Hey, there was Rudy
Rudy's a guy Rudy fucks with Rudy Rudy. Oh
See he's on point. You like nigga. I'm about the pop over for me
Hey, rude.
Really likes to like curl up and see I like how you got the open door policy and if they leave they leave if they come back
They come back. So so what if that cat left? All right?
You got an open door policy. This is what people misunderstand about you
You said you got a cat door that means an open door policy to any cat that you ever own now if they leave they leave
So what?
I want somebody else to tell whatever
Mean it's so crazy. It's like yes cats catch mice. I mean they they're it's called the open door policy
You don't you don't really own none of them. Do you know you take care of them? I
Cats own me. I'm more their slave. Yeah, exactly. You just take care of them in mind
That's how I see it. I see if you got an open door policy in your house with cats
You don't own them. You just take care of cats. Yeah, I mean
They can come and go as they please they come and go as you please. Yeah
Yep, and uh, cuz I and they're this neighborhood is not like where the things on it
There's not a feral cap population here. There's no but they try to say like are you you lost your cat?
No, it's a fuck out of you being a troll. We all know it dead people say
People say, you know, I'm irresponsible blah blah blah. It's like, you know, it's like, you know, he will be a volume psyche
Was that my volume?
Yeah, just a little bit.
You're a little low to me. You's loud outside.
Okay, here. Is that better?
There we go. I have my mic right there. Let me see if it's connected. Yeah, I think my mic's connected. Let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see.
Yeah, so let me see. My mic is here.
Yeah, I had a lot to talk about today, but like, fuck that shit.
See, there's a difference when I'm joining somebody's page. I'm bad respectful, unless we talk about the same bullshit that I'm gonna, you know, I'm gonna lift myself to what I gotta say.
But then when I'm on my page, it's like, you see the difference, right? I took a whole lot of shit.
I'm gonna go I'm gonna check it to see if somebody hit everybody because it's like
The other day that happened the other day like I looked and it's like someone had hit like they went back
Oh, they attacked me attack that page of the guy. I told you play the video
They think on the video. So I know exactly what part he shrikes. So I edit it right before I stopped
Alleged these panels, and I got it on Facebook. I got it here and there. I got it in a couple of places and
I'm gonna I'm never gonna stop showing that picture of that guy come across on me just because he saw me
I didn't touch him. He just saw me
Okay
Okay, so here's his band. Here's his band Charlotte the harlot scatman John Tony wins again. No, I don't got nobody been
The real big let them all come with a troll accounts and block them. Okay. Yeah, it looks like everybody's blocked is blocked
I don't see anybody. Yeah. No, look, you know, you ban them, you know, like get the fuck out of you know
Six gone. Remember that night six had the whole panel of pack you open like six channels just to join your show at the same time
Yeah, well, you know what and the people came in doxing and so, you know, I just put some like put some block words and it's like
You know, I've been dox. I've been dox. We've been dox the only person that hasn't been dox is Christine
Yeah, and you know Kate the turtle actually I said, oh, I'll pay for Chris. I know she's putting a little ward out heard
I heard about that sort of picture. She put a little ward out
I'm not gonna stop me because you know, Kate Kate Kate
Kate got a little ward out for beaters. Um, I mean
Christine's
Right. Yep. And it's like that's not our fault that she wrote that I'm just saying I'm just repeating what happened. Exactly. Yeah
I'm yeah, it's like yeah, and they're gonna blame you're gonna say I'm gonna blame us for something else like he's trying to promote this and that and this and that
No, I'm just repeating what happened. Hey, actually, you know, I'm on this channel. I'm almost able to monetize this channel
Just need to get I'm at 657 out of 1,000 subscribers. I'm 65% there for the subscribers
But I'm at 4,000. I'm at 5,000 watch hours on this channel already. So
Not too shabby not too shabby. So I'm gonna I can monetize this
You know why because they behave it's still still got progress right now, so it's not not too shabby bad
Yeah, yeah, I think I'll just move my music videos and stuff to a separate
Top content I had well last night I had 600 people
Views on last night's show
And then you know, thank you. No, I heard from old school. So I'm blind for you. Hey, it is
Yeah, I'm lying to you. Hey does. Yeah. Yeah, it's like I'm lying to you. Hey, it is
Oh gosh, I already I got drunk off that one sip of alcohol
Stop playing with your boy. Yo, I'm supposed to like you bro
For a minute, and I just I just did that bullshit back then psyche with ghost
I mean God and what happened Michael and shit. I really felt offended at one point
But then I was like, all right, this is like, let me see how many people will leave or follow me out
It's like drop to six people. I mean, it's like, I don't know it's like I don't understand these numbers
It's like, you know, and the numbers after six. Yeah
Drop to six people from 30. All right. Everybody wants to be this. You got a hundred and seven
Okay, well, I mean, I think they're probably talking about me over there and so I would like you know
I usually like to like, you know, you know
Drink that cup water. Let's have some fun. We're gonna talk shit tonight
And everybody else gonna come back when they join it. That's when they join it
They get you only only two hours it nigga. My battery's good. I'm gonna talk shit. You gonna talk shit. Fuck that
Watch some videos and laugh
Let's find a drink. I'm going to spy on you. I'm drinking too. Okay. I'm just going to spy on the background a little bit to see what's going on
I'm gonna see if my because I'm sure my name is being brought up all over the place
Yes, I think you ain't gonna give up just because six people here fuck that
Stains is like also like streaming, you know, they're doing this RV stuff. Yeah, let them scream bro
Hey, you should stop being like nice about shit. Nigga fuck that strike the nigga. They do any reputation. Oh, yeah
Yeah, like fuck them fuck them. Okay, so, but you know who's nice to me is Victoria J is nice
But who you want to be do you want to be the asshole?
Well, I'm trying to be the nice guy now when I be the bad guy you're going to be the good guys
Cues someone seems jealous. Oh, yeah, I seem jealous
He's making fun of me
And he wanted to put your cock in his mouth. That's why he's talking all that shit psyche
That's how I feel. I feel he wanted to put your cock in his mouth. Wow
You know, that's why people say so much around those door. No, he like you said he said he rather fuck he rather fuck you
They're fucking chick
Who says that in their right minds, oh my god, well, they're just talking about shit. I mean
It's boring
I'm not listening. I'm just watching. Yeah, it's boring over there. I just looked and it's like they're right
They talk about he's it's cute. I mean, it's like, okay
Yeah, it's so it's so so it was like a what oh seven would I look for that?
Well, you said that I was at 103 so they jump back over here as you know the punch is better stop playing
Or are you recording stop watching? Hey, hey, but hey, fuck it. Thank you for the view. Hello. Goodbye
Exactly, exactly. Well, yeah, who cares? I mean, it's like really it's like
Hey, I still you know, are you say how I used to say it? Oh, thank you for building my algorithm. Goodbye. Yeah
Thank you and goodbye. So this is my doing goodbye
Did you see that? There's my panda
Fuck the haters man psyche. I wouldn't make it to 4,000 if I gave up that fast so much. Hey, I had psyche come on
Yep, look at that. What you go through is nothing compared to what I went through
Pretty cool, huh? I look like some crazy shit like yeah
What that shit says it is there's 72 names and he like there's okay
So they take out of like I guess something that Moses said
There's one thing you do
What would you do? I don't know why that question popped up in my head, but one thing I could do on earth
If there's one thing you could do for the earth
What would you do for the earth? I would you know, I would I'll get rid of all like the like the I guess the fucking
Those things that that a trap fish. So what would these to be on the these to be on the endolphin?
You make me you said something with fish and water so the water be clean
Yeah, I'm gonna clean the water, you know, basically all water be removed of all trash
When we great if it was like, you know, the water was like fresh water like the oceans
It's fresh and we could just drink the water. So the ocean's so clean that you could drink from it pure
You don't have to boil it. Imagine that
There's a lot of fish pee in there, you know
Yeah
Have a fun anyway, like I yeah, it's like I don't it's like really it's like even if I have one
friend here, which is like, which is like you, you know, it's like that that is like that is enough for me
Like it's like you know when I first got here how everybody should be like easy to this easy to that in your time
You'd like well
Let me tell myself
I know and also I'm a little bit of a paranoid too and so sometimes I went up in a paranoid state.
At the beginning it was so much hate for me being here because I was traveling to other panels
and they was trying to, what did you say?
Now boycott me out of every panel I go through no matter where.
And now look at the difference nobody even saying shit now shut the fuck up, right?
I mean his boy the boycotting is really really stupid in my opinion
It is just like you know what is like, you know
I said that I said that because it was the boycott of situations. I'm saying I happened to be way back with so
Remember we're not came here. It happened
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean what for what I mean it's like cuz Christina, you know
It's like it's like bitching about stuff and oh, how do you like I never I never boycott it
I never told anybody to where to go or what to do and so it's like and really people have the right to go wherever they want
Oh, no, but the question I actually the other day how many times like Christine came to your panel knowing that she wasn't welcome here
But she still can't take in a name got her opinion. I still let her up. I still let her up
I mean, I let you know, she wasn't welcome in many times. She came
Yeah, it's like I'm talking all that shit about you bro. Exactly. Oh, hi, babe
And the same she's doing the same thing to me now. She's like, oh, don't make easy up
Don't do this don't do that if she's controlling people's panels by paying paying them out paying a panel out
Because she got money she's trying to use by everybody out. Yeah, I believe she's doing the same thing computer right now
I think beaters is taking our money and like, all right, I'm gonna get sober
pay me I'm gonna help you and
Pay my panel and stuff like that. Like I think that's happening with her too
Like Christine is manipulating through money. So anybody want a panel pay for how like Christine. Yeah
She does it. Well, she kicks it. She's one kick me off of Sam Man's panel and and
You know it all and then and beat is like well my oh guess you know, you know
The real hero behind you know boycotting psyche is actually Sam Man because he kicks he kicks psyche off
It's yeah, I can't say man off my panel like a hundred times like in a night, you know
It's like oh, I wouldn't even let him up, bro
Like you gotta understand that leave your haters gone like you got no I don't you don't want no associated with them
Don't ever associate them
Let them go to their panel open some shit and then that's defamation over there
You know saying then whatever the case might be whatever, you know, let's fuck them niggas, bro. That's how I roll. Yeah, fuck my haters
definitely
Hey, what's up shit my people. I'm not gonna block you my people's gonna let you talk to the limit
They're gonna be like goodbye. It's buffering. I don't know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm not sure if it's buffering
I'll talk to my haters psyche. That's
Simple like all right not so long go up the reveal what happened, right?
To me when I got doxxed right I got doxxed and then the reveal happened with it with with with the partners of the Doxxon
Started fighting so it's before then Christine was like oh, I will never be on a panel week easy again
I'm avoiding him. I'm doing this and that so she was a suspect in the Doxxon
So when the review came out that this person did the Doxxon
And I jumped on panel with the guy that was doing the revealing who comes up. Oh
Christine she's ready God. She was never gonna be on panel with me
But since the doxin happened and she's one of the people I believe did the doxin she jumped up to defend herself
Why would you do that because the reveal was happening and she didn't want it to get exposed
So she jumped up and she had to protect herself
Yep, oh, yeah, she always has to get her like little two cents then or whatever
But, you know, pretty lame, let me see, yeah, so let me see, let me just check you out.
When I did turn on that show, her show, I heard, oh my god, you know, Psyche, there's Psyche
there, and it's like, oh, in the other day, I didn't hear my name, and all of a sudden,
she's like, oh, Psyche's about to start, and they're like, you mean Samman?
And she's like, I said Samman, they're like, no, you said Psyche, she's like, oh, whoops.
People give themselves up in funny ways. That's all I gotta say. Yeah, I mean you gave your whole self up that that was you
You know
Matthew probably manipulated you can't go with your story, but
That's that's how I see it. I see it was Christine and Matthew
That's why I'm not stopping and that's why the boy he got sweet for me and they revealed it
He saw me your face was the cat
He's literally you didn't have to try you literally
Perfect
Little you got a cat mask like you one of those. Um, you know what those movies when they got the half mask on
That's you know, oh
Well, you're a pre-master a mask. That's just close some shit like that. I don't know. Yeah
I'm a cat. There you go. Yeah. Yeah. I mean it's a game jumped up right when right with the reveal
What's happening cuz she didn't want no more of the reveal to happen
No, oh my gosh. Yeah, it's like oh
But it's like yeah, it's like yeah as for this community if it's like it's so it's so easy to throw me out of it or whatever
I would never part of it begin with also
Thank you. I got you those thank you like remember I said, yo you was at three and then we brought you back up
We helped you know, but we're gonna bring you back up no matter what
Yeah, I mean, you know, there was no way I say time for like new people in here. Anyway, you know, it's like
Listen, psyche the truth shall be revealed in the righteous shop prosper
I do that
Long as you know, you're not the wrong one combo always have it back with justice
Right, right, right, right, and I am I'm definitely like I'm just standing up for truth
I'm not trying to
Not not like trying to be like remember that like I always I believe in karma
the God of karma will always come back and
Patience is the key to virtue right be patient psyche
Everything will be revealed do time. I got it. Keep on moving. Okay, so
Moving oh take another zip of my time. Come on now. I will but I haven't have it. I haven't have a chaser
I'm gonna come on. Oh, come on. I finished my time finish the my time
Then go with that if you want to mix it up finish one and then go with the other
Those are like mix it. Oh, you know, you got to finish one complete. Come on
You got this I'm telling you psyche you got this you got this those are good
Those are worth it. It's worth being fucked up. We're like you're fucked up
You get the logon I see you come like fuck easy. I want to know what I fuck you and make it on the beach
I'm telling you
Pop the other one if you want to mix it mix it you're gonna get fucked up even worse
There you go that use it as a um, what's that shit a chaser? Yeah, that's it. He's too strong
They use it as a chaser, but take a little zips not OD gops. All right. Oh my god
Do me a favor because I don't want you fucked up fucked up. I want you already
Oh
Tell me by the time you get to long island ice team. That's the next one. You're gonna be easy and now I know what I fuck
He was naked. You know today. You're gonna know you're gonna learn you're gonna learn today today gonna learn
I'm here with you, bro. I'm gonna get drunk. Okay. Yeah
I'm gonna put up all the phone to charge right now just in case the battery's low. Is that 60% now? I'm good
Okay, I'm not jumping on that one if this phone dies. I'm jumping on that one then kick me in this phone
I'm here. I'm here. We hit thank you. I I I don't know. Oh my gosh
I'm telling you if those shit just drops like you may have to have yo by the time you finish that one you'll be like, all right
Um
I'm about to pass out. I'm dying to find a story got those again. Oh my god
I was on vacation when I took those I was going I think I'm gonna put a background on cuz I think people like when I have a
Background on you see how about this one like the eye? I like the eye
Here that
What do you think?
That's like my eye color it's kind of like hazel it is my eye color right there. No, I got hazel eyes you do me too
Look at my eye. I'll show you
I got I got he's wise color before for yeah
I'll see you
Yo, yo, yo, you guys like I got his life. I'm just like ease
Yeah
Let me and I don't think I'm promoting my discord. So I'm gonna put my I'm gonna put my link to my discord to for the show
Yeah, I'm gonna put my link for my discord
Stream yard. Okay. Here we go
or actually YouTube, okay, and
Because this is my backup channel, so I don't have this
Hey, I'm leaving a wizard. Yo, I'm on psyche pull up right now, man. They go like pull up
We don't fuck all this question. They should ask me on live. I mean, I'm not in the booth all this
You should write here we go
There, okay. Yeah, fuck the boycott. No, that's got a question for me. I don't want to hand it right now
I don't write through that shit
Okay, here we go. I guess somebody panicked
Somebody close this shit
Okay, I'm gonna post my my league in my discord. So everyone with everyone will see okay. Let's see. Okay. There we go
Where's my discord here? We go to psyche
Everyone
At everyone, okay, what someone said
There we go
Give a guess
And they're also still cover on there. Oh, what's up? They're accusing me already
Yeah, straight up
Acts if I took Steven Fender I want to go look right now. He's one of them there, but I don't know about the other one
Let me take that shit
Where
On on his back up panel some shit
Who's mine?
No, not yours. Oh, I'm sorry. Okay. Oh BTV's or some shit like let me know
No
It was somebody's back up probably in the cues of what because I could show I could show I
Could show
Actually, I'm telling you I can show it. I didn't strike Steven's panel. It would have been up there. It would have been
I didn't strike him niggas or whoever's blaming me
Tell who strikes I'm chilling y'all. I've been home. I've been I've been cast to her home
He came my mom's again late. I'm back and I'm happy. I'm back to my normal life
Nah, he said he can't get on his panel some shit was going on with family can't get on and
He's in up his backup panel just case they better go to the other end of these niggas stop trying to blame me
Niggas math need his food stamps and
Prestige nigga the fuck is wrong with you nigga don't trust that bitch
By the way, I just want to show people like I think like you know
Okay, yeah, they would it was it says when you get strike it says who does it to you. Yeah, and
Or else it's like they're supposed to tell you. Yeah, it's a copyright
I haven't taken class because of the mafia video and I might I might get it back
But I'm gonna edit it. I'm gonna clip it. I'm gonna clip the part
And you try to strike me for out and then I'm gonna repose it
No, but oh he say he's doing classes or some shit
Yeah, you gotta do classes. That's what happened to me just now. Look
Quiz you take a quiz about you. All right. All right. Who's up? All right. All right. Make sense right now
I just got strike for some shit my video got taken down
Um, he got strikes of some shit his video or his case got taken down now
We gotta go
Because because the same person we don't like is striking us that that makes sense
No, that's all he say can't go live. He say have to do classes or some shit
But he say got move back up. He say
Whatever they told me the same shit. They said they said um take classes, but y'all you still go live
You can still post and everything
Know
This is a warning don't do it again
So all I'm gonna do is clip out the part that they he said was a threat and that part and I told you I was gonna tell you
Only so I'm not gonna say it
But that part you didn't tell me shit nigga. Let me tell you I say yeah. Yeah, I forgot to tell you
Yo, but now but yo
He can't go live you can't do remember
Got to be Matthew your food says well, I swear to God everything I love that's not about folk don't blame that on me
Don't put the blame on me. Don't you put that blame on me?
What I'm a justice to do
Don't put that anybody knows who the only person I've been attacking since God knows
Yeah
Yeah, bro, but yeah, now we're gonna chill. What's up? What's good with you?
You so psyche psyche got covered right now, nigga
He's drinking cold water
I'm gonna get someone with Delos. I like me. You're like lucky. I can't get cold water right now
Cuz if I could find it, I would have bought it with you nigga
Oh, thank you
Right now he's getting wasted right now
Yeah, nigga, I don't I don't go I don't turn panels like that. I know you haven't been live in all that
I know I was over here years, but yeah, but then and then I he didn't start so I am
Came right did he go live around 420?
They believe the bull just go live around 420. Oh
No, I don't watch that in your shit. I'm not subscribed to them. So
So so so so I'm not gonna talk to but I just look them up, right? So it said he was live
around 420 I
Program my shit to be 420. So every time I go live he's gonna try to go live. I just I just peeped it
Nesh, I mean I'm not stupid nigga with you. Oh every time he goes live
Oh, you're perfect. I think a follow that they could follow me to different panels little faggot. Who is excuse my language
He's a little bitch boy nigga. He's a he's a boy a boy term bitch
Yeah, BTB
Boy turn bitch. Uh-huh. You want to follow me like bitch? I'm like fucking state gay
Memorize they gave it up the fucking shirt. He's like easy. Come on easy. I'll send back the seven dollars
Oh, yeah, I was like, yeah, all right.
So like y'all take it is like showing his tank top blowing
you kisses you said, and you I know you was ripped that day.
So I know that wasn't a lie.
I know I'm such a I'm such a like a whore.
I mean, really, sometimes you are.
Sometimes you're little whore, but I know.
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like,
we tell let me tell you up me and you's
going to have such a fun time.
You're gonna be have
Psychic shit the other day, right?
Who me?
Yeah
Well, what I said about you are psychics
You played off you somebody else and they had that duck feet
The what
Hey, look at me and psyche a the dawn's like Donald Duck, you know, so it's dawn
the dawn of that quack quack while we're drinking on the most Delos playing poker you're hurt. Yeah
Yeah, so there we are. We need to have your poker face song when you go
Doing the quacks go on. I'll put I'll put I'll put less in there too
Lessons you make one with all three of us right now psyche
Got it. See last you part of the quack squad nigga like no, bro. I'm not told shit about you. Who said that?
No, it was a picture like that that picture you got right now. They came up with that picture
Yeah, it's Arthur Arthur because that's a big that's a period of Arthur's picture. Okay. Yeah, I do Arthur duck feet
Nigga, that's all I'm the only one that got that nigga. I'm originally my shit
Wow, the word lounging not original, but yeah, I'm making fun of him like you know
I made on track a book
That's what
We love the psyche I lay over white
Yes, you got the gun. I'm chillin smoking. Yeah, I'm in drag
I'm doing drag. Do you like your hair with a drag queen?
What drag queen duck for the drag queen duck with a
half human half robot
duck and
Then put one duck smoking and drinking on modulo
Okay, half robot duck. Hey, okay
That's Alex Alex
No, nigga. That's us three nigga. He wanted to be a drag queen. He's just said it
He's a pretty like that
You you you got the picture of a half robot half human so I said that and me. I'm chilling with smoking drinking on motel. Oh
Yeah, guys, I got I got this one. I said
Okay, well, I mean this one came out
You're like psyche take a zip take a zip with me psyche. I will this one came out wrong though. Look at this one
No, that's fusion nigga, that's you me and psyche nigga
Yeah, but you write it put one duck and then two duck three duck like that
They each duck got to have their own description that's how you do it's like you trust me. I know
Are you doing to that cat easy
They get that same man, nigga, you
It's time to do the dude the dual
I Summon Hateron with a magic card of
I got it. I got it. Here we are already. I got it. I got it. Yeah, I'm ready. I'm ready ready dropping like it's hot
Dropping like it's hot
You're right. Take that my time dip. Take that my time dip. Come on, psyche. I'm ready. Take a zip
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Hey, oh my god, that should be funny as fuck. I'm laughing my ass off
Let me see. I'm gonna do it. Let me see if I can make it. I'll make one of Sam and Ambedo. Let me see
That's a nice one. That's me. You were likes. Oh shit now. We need one with Alex. I will duck. This is NYPD bend over
I'm gonna throw you in that bushes. Oh
Okay
Holy fuckering
We some funny-ass niggas psyche you funny-ass niggas. Thank you. Take a little fucker
Okay, one second. No big screen. Take this now. Go big screen. I'd like to zip in if you zip together, you know what I'm saying?
Rock! Rock! Have you chased already? Have you chased already? Have you chased already?
I'm already here. Let me see. I'll do one more picture.
I didn't even see a big screen, but I want to see. My eyesight is bad.
Hang on, guys. Is this right here? Do you want the Alex in there too? Here.
Yeah, Saiki's the gangster, he's like, you're fucked back.
I went, ganks the dogs.
Nah, I think I'm the gangster.
Well, Saiki, you more the classic.
You like a classic, man.
Yeah, I'm like the Latino one with the
Second to the right you're the first to the right. Yeah, I'm not on the far right. I'm no far right
I'm far right and then there's less in the middle and then there's Alex. Ah shit
You're you're the Latino. You're the Latino
In the world
In the world where quacks run everything and we are quacking out
Yeah, quacking out. Okay, so let me I'll put us I'll put a big screen in here. We go. Here we go. Okay. There we go. Okay, so
I'm ready. I'm ready. Take a sip. Let's go. Let's go. Take a sip. Okay. Here we go. It's small
So it's gonna disappear fast because you're gonna get fucked up good. Oh
Oh, take the chaser. There you go. All right. Oh
Finished it that one's done. That was done long island. I was tea number two round
One more I got you
Just a pain. I'm not trying to get you drunk drunk, but let me know I got I got you
We're having a party over here. Oh, yeah, we're having trouble right now. Where the fuck let's go
You're gonna see a reality Nancy. Yeah reality Nancy. I thought she didn't like me
I don't know a lot of people like this like to me after the Christine at you
But you gotta understand she pushed herself into that situation to be a victim
If somebody's crashing now, you don't try to be miss mama mama to everybody especially for a psychopath like me
Well as they call me as they call me
That day the police didn't come right
Or did they come or what happened? No, no, man. Listen, even the other day when I pressed the guy from box in me
They came I almost they said almost a half an hour to hour later some shit like that
Then then then hour later I go to the store I go back outside
And they arrest the guy right the detectives and NYPD officers. You'll rest a guy
Right in front of me now if they had my description here grand and this and that whatever I'll put a hat on and
And and they know me and the guy knows my name he gave
You know, he might have gave that information up on the phone call when I walked away who says not
You know say until somebody gets this phone call and I know my people who's can't reach out and get this
911 phone call that he made you go get the full 911 a phone call
so
Yeah, I mean, it's like you're controversial. I mean, it's like I have controversial people on the show
I mean, it's like they know I know I'm like ever oppressed Howard Stern for having on the KKK guy, right?
And it's like and basically
Or or talking on the phone with the guy that was a confessed to murders and the and all this stuff and it's like so
I can like talk to anybody. I don't care who's in my chat, you know
Garfield I have a picture of Lola eating lasagna. She looks like Garfield. I said lasagna. You said Garfield the funny ass
You have fish tacos. I can go get me fish tacos right now alive, but oh
Let me see. I mean, I should do that. I should get dressing right down there, right? I should do a psyche. Yeah
Give you a live broadcast of walking down Castle Hill. But if I won't I'm gonna get on the bus without paying for it
How about that people? Yeah, do it. Do it. Oh my god. That's like that's like a 420, right? Okay, so let me see
Yeah, I know it's a crazy
Okay, so
Okay
Okay, and this is easy and I right now
This is easy and I right now
Okay, oh here we go it did it I did it I'm shocked. Okay. Look at this
Okay, I'm gonna put on here
There's eating the fish taco and eating the lasagna.
There we go.
I'm going to put on a quick video.
I'm going to take a little break.
But I think you'll enjoy this one.
This is actually like a really ultra realistic one.
And run if you don't like my videos.
Okay.
But I think you'll like this one.
I got it.
I'm still here, I'm just getting dressed.
Thank you, you missed it.
Okay, I'm putting on a song real quick here.
Just so you can hear the song, it's a good song.
Here we go.
Okay, got it, here we go.
Okay, do you see it on the screen yet?
Let me see.
Oh yeah, you do, okay.
Enjoy.
just as lost as you don't flinch i've got the scars to prove it through a doorway cracked
inside my skull let the shadows crawl whispering fall every thought brought its own ghost friends
I'm gonna finish this bare first psyche and then I'm gonna head out because I don't want it to be warm by the time I get out.
But let me know when you pop the Long Island Iced tea. If you're gonna pop that one or the sobae, return first.
I know this Long Island Iced tea is strong, so watch it.
I usually go to the space psyche and I get a three-course meal and they're like trying to like $50 or like
I was playing cancer, but once I swear the sky was white
marching out of the dream so quiet not giving up hope it's better we're
prisms of soul
Hey, you'll like this one easy.
Machiavelli.
That one was nice.
I was listening to it while we were getting dressed.
That was nice.
Not even a little bit.
I was on his right.
I'm like, you're invisible, not weak.
Just too available, too eager.
Given to people who don't respect you,
but the world doesn't care about your heart.
It cares about your value.
And if you can't control perception,
you'll spend your life being used.
Overlooked.
people judge with their eyes not their hands they see results not your struggle
they see outcomes not your intention and honestly they don't care about your sacrifice about your purity
about your good heart you want respect demonstrate strength you want loyalty prove value you want
I'm saying stop expecting the world to reward you for being nice look around look at them
The ones who get ahead on always moral that's strategic they understand power is perception not purity
If you feel invisible, it's not under valuation for the big screen. Hello. You got to go get my fish tacos
What are you doing on here?
Bro, stop acting tough, bro!
What's your look, man?
Wee wee wee wee!
Change starting now. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. They need me more than I need them. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. They need me more than I need them. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I control my value. I
I go with the bus, if I can't see the bus in my point of view psyche, I'm just gonna walk it.
Mackey or Belly watch the most powerful, they're with the ones constantly in every one's face, they were selective, strategic, hard to reach
Your availability is killing you when you respond to everything immediately, when you never say no, you're training people to disrespect you
You're teaching them your time means nothing, that you're desperate for their attention and desperation repels power
Master strategic withdrawal don't answer every call immediately let some messages sit say no to requests that don't serve you create space between yourself and others
Something magical happens people start wondering about you. They start respecting your time
They start valuing your presence because it's no longer
Can't wait to create curiosity curiosity
How the fuck do you say a desire desire creates power stop pouring yourself into people who give nothing back stop
being emotionally available to everyone when you become scarce not from arrogance but self-respect
you force people to earn access to you the ones who don't let them go they were never adding value
anyway you teach people how to treat you by what you tolerate if you tolerate disrespect
you get more if you tolerate being taken for granted that's exactly what will happen but when
you pull back when you become selective when you operate from abundance not scarcity you
My time is currency, my presence is precious, my energy is mine, I control access, I control
생각나요 생각나요
오 예?
생각나요?
생각나요
If you're not hungry, then take your portion and give it back to them.
That's it, dude, they've been looking out.
Yeah, they've been looking out.
Alright, that's good.
This is how power actually works, I can only show this 500 years ago where those people ignored it, wanted to believe that this was fair, that kindness wins, that hard work is enough, but you're not most people you're here because you want the truth, and the truth is this is the game of the world.
Whether you're playing or when they're being played
I control my value
I control my value, stricty
Powerful and inevitable
I control my value
I am irreplaceable
I am undeniable
I am the one playing
Not the one being played
I control my value
Look at this Sucio, look at this Sucio, what up Sucio?
It's good. Let me hold that. I might go get some fish tacos, bro. I go I go to the building and bring that back
Yeah, I mean trying to bring that back. I want to get fish tacos
He's just cute guys. I'm not wait for the buses. I should be coming. It's the one stop away
No, it's one stop away. Fuck it. It's one stop away. The bus
No, you remember my shit, nigga
I'll give it to you, I'll give it to you back to me.
But you gotta put gas in this.
Like you don't have a seat for like $3.
I think I'm getting off for free.
I think I must be like $40, nigga, $50.
Back, back, yeah, I know you.
Yeah, hold on, shorty coming up.
Oh, there you go.
Yeah, yeah, I ain't gonna violate shorty, nigga.
Never violate the shorties, nigga.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's all.
I'll highlight you.
If you're pulling up tonight, nigga, let's go check.
Let's go check.
Yeah, I want to check tonight.
Niggas Friday, man, nigga.
Well hit up hit up
Everybody
Yeah, give me give me a time. Hold on
Easy easy the picture look at the screen
Okay, you're right. No, bro. They take it easy bro all day every day
Easy is the picture
How about a tip or how about I think I should go get some food and back so fast
That's us
Yes, hey, hey, hey, it's just been a second
The one thank you
For free did anybody say you know free you an actual IRL and it's like you know, but people would rather like listen to beat is
No beautiful day over there
Okay time to read me it's more than zero ignore me. Hey people that aren't here. I don't want to hear anyway
All right, what you said, Saki?
We have one viewer.
Oh, Ferru, Ferru?
Yeah.
God damn.
Almost I mean when it drops to zero. I'm gonna end but uh, I bet if you want to end it
Yo, let me know how everything is after the fact like
I mean wow, it's like I guess the cue boycott is working
I guess what what if you go in love with this nigger or something like that? I don't know
I have no clue. He's a here if you want to make me a if he's a hater let him be a hater. That's it
I'm gonna play, actually, do you saw that Alexander's video
she made?
I don't know if you saw it.
No, I don't, I don't watch her page.
Okay, what, look at this, you'll see it, you'll love it.
Cause actually it's on the peer,
like we go to the peer with Q.
So I can have them on my show still, here we go.
This is called, let me see, this is on her channel,
called IP2WikiInfo, let me see, I think it's on Emma.
This is called Join the Cult.
All those under mayors made this and I think you will enjoy it. Let me just bring it right up. Okay. I'm second
Yeah, I love it. It's Chris Murray
If you want to home if you want any I know from which is let me know next time we get
Here here you go. I'll maybe I'll play this on the way out actually here. We go. Thank you for being here easy here
Watch this watch this check this out. You love it. I promise
Check this out. Okay got it. Here we go
City can see me before I even spoke I don't know about that, but I'm still here
i've been walking in circles baby losing my direction same old face is selling perfect projections
everybody swears that they got the truth but i don't even know what i'm supposed to do then
you show up on my feet like a premonition cards on the table digital visions say boy i read what
you're avoiding yeah you got a way of making silence feel loud they say you're dangerous
You said join the girl, no fear, no pressure
Yeah, you say come see me don't overthink it
But I freeze every time I get close to the edge of it cuz the world's got opinions on what this means
And I don't even know what I'm feeling in yeah, maybe it's more than illusion something bout you got me questioning conclusions
Every symbol every line you draw feels like truth I've been running from and the voices in my head keep telling me
No pain, no pressure, just you're getting closer to your own sin
And they'll talk, they'll judge, but what's that worth
When you ain't even living in your own world?
Join the cult, no shame, no hiding
No more running, no more dividing
Step out the script, they built body, fall, find your truth
Join the cult
This is your turning I laugh it off but my chest starts burning
All this time I've been standing still While the world keeps asking me to feel
If I stay, I'm safe but I'm fading If I go, I might stop changing
Maybe that's the risk I need to finally be something real
No more asking
that you find yourself when you join the cause.
no skin off my tits, whatever, but one more. Here you go. Shout out to Alexandra. Thank
you for being my friend, you know.
Then a signal cut the noise in two
Soft but sharp like a truth I knew
Every fracture lit up in gold
Every story we never told
Time been backward just to let you through
Every lost frequency tuned to you
RETURN!
future soft disguise you don't speak you transmit truth rewriting pain into
something
Finally chose no more signal lost in fear
Never